# Mohamed Manar Khirallah IT Networks Engineer

## **Personal Details**

Email: Manar.kh.it@gmail.com Phone: (+964) 7518181675 LinkedIn: Mohamed Manar Khirallah

Date of Birth: 15/09/1995 Location: Iraq, Erbil Marital status: Single

**Summary** 

**Experience:** +2 Years of total experience.

**Hard Skills:** IT Network Engineer, IT Help Desk, Information Technology, Technical Support, CCNA R&S, MCSA, System Administration, Windows Server, IP/TCP, Operating Systems, Microsoft Office, Software Installation, IOT experience (Raspberry Pi 3, Arduino).

**Soft Skills:** Self-Learner, Teamwork, Good Communication, Excellent Researcher, Creative Thinking, Problem Solving, Analytical Skills, Troubleshoot.

**Languages:** Arabic (Native), English (Professional working proficiency)

# **Experience**

IT Support Engineer at Khallouf Trading Company - Syria

Jan 2019 - Dec 2020 (2 yrs.)

- Installing and Configuring computer systems and applications, maintain them with latest updates.
- Troubleshooting and Resolving technical issues and providing direct support to users.
- Come up with new ideas to solve and develop the work environment.
- Test new features on Virtual Machines using VMware before deploying them into production.
- Maintain and Monitor security cameras, Attendance system and keep them up to date.



### Data Entry Specialist at Takamol ISP - Syria

Sep 2018 - Dec 2018 (4 mos.)

- Receiving, processing and updating data from customers plus preparing relevant reports as needed
- Accurately enter data into corresponding fields within various software programs
- Providing general data entry support for other teammates

#### Education



#### Al-Ba'ath University

2014 - 2019

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science, IT Systems & Network Engineering

## **Certificates**

- Cisco Certified Network Associate Routing and Switching (CCNA) Syrian Virtual University SVU
- Microsoft Certified Solutions Associate (MCSA) Lynda.com (Self-Learned)
- Google IT Support Professional Certificate Specialization Coursera
- Cisco Networking Basics Specialization Coursera
- Excel Skills for Business: Intermediate I Coursera